const quizAnime = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question:
      "What is the name of the main character in the anime 'One Piece'?",
    options: [
      "Monkey D. Luffy",
      "Monkey D. Garp",
      "Monkey D. Dragon",
      "Monkey D. Ace",
    ],
    answer: "Monkey D. Luffy",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "What is the name of the main character in the anime 'Naruto'?",
    options: [
      "Sasuke Uchiha",
      "Sakura Haruno",
      "Kakashi Hatake",
      "Naruto Uzumaki",
    ],
    answer: "Naruto Uzumaki",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What is the name of the main character in the anime 'Bleach'?",
    options: [
      "Rukia Kuchiki",
      "Ichigo Kurosaki",
      "Renji Abarai",
      "Uryu Ishida",
    ],
    answer: "Ichigo Kurosaki",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "What is the name of the main character in the anime 'Dragon Ball Z'?",
    options: ["Vegeta", "Goku", "Gohan", "Trunks"],
    answer: "Goku",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "What is the name of the main character in the anime 'One Punch men'?",
    options: ["Genos", "Tatsumaki", "King", "Saitama"],
    answer: "Saitama",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "What is the name of the main character in the anime 'My Hero Academia'?",
    options: [
      "Izuku Midoriya",
      "Katsuki Bakugo",
      "Ochaco Uraraka",
      "Shoto Todoroki",
    ],
    answer: "Izuku Midoriya",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "What is the name of the main character in the anime 'Attack on Titan'?",
    options: [
      "Mikasa Ackerman",
      "Armin Arlert",
      "Eren Yeager",
      "Levi Ackerman",
    ],
    answer: "Eren Yeager",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      "What is the name of the main character in the anime 'Tokyo Ghoul'?",
    options: [
      "Hideyoshi Nagachika",
      "Soraka ken",
      "Ken Kaneki",
      "Kaneki Hideyoshi",
    ],
    answer: "Ken Kaneki",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "What is the name of the main character in the anime 'Death Note'?",
    options: ["Light Yagami", "L", "Ryuk", "Misa Amane"],
    answer: "Light Yagami",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "What is the name of the main character in the anime 'Hunter x Hunter'?",
    options: ["Killua Zoldyck", "Hisoka Morow", "Gon Freecss", "Kurapika"],
    answer: "Gon Freecss",
  },
];

export default quizAnime;
